Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2016
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Tam Travers, violin, Mabel Kwan, piano, Chris Wild, violoncello, Stephen Solook, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, and Greg Beyer, percussion) in a performance of Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4520.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_236.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Tam Travers, violin, Mabel Kwan, piano, Chris Wild, violoncello, Stephen Solook, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, and Emma Hospelhorn, flute) in a performance of Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 black and white digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4522 copy.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_237.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Tam Travers, violin, Mabel Kwan, piano, Chris Wild, violoncello, Stephen Solook, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, and Emma Hospelhorn, flute) in a performance of Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4523 copy.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_238.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Tam Travers, violin, Mabel Kwan, piano, Chris Wild, violoncello, Stephen Solook, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, and Emma Hospelhorn, flute) in a performance of Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Tif Susan Ung.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_239.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Tam Travers, violin, Mabel Kwan, piano, Chris Wild, violoncello, Stephen Solook, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, and Emma Hospelhorn, flute) in a performance of Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name UNG.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_240.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Tam Travers, violin, Mabel Kwan, piano, Chris Wild, violoncello, Stephen Solook, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, and Greg Beyer, percussion) in a performance of Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4524.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_241.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung acknowledges Michael Lewanski, conductor, Susan Ung, viola, and Ensemble Dal Niente (Mabel Kwan, piano, Tam Travers, violin, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Stephen Solook, percussion, and Emma Hospelhorn, flute) after a performance of Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4526.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_242.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung acknowledges Michael Lewanski, conductor, Susan Ung, viola, and Ensemble Dal Niente (Mabel Kwan, piano, Tam Travers, violin, Chris Wild, violoncello, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Stephen Solook, percussion, and Emma Hospelhorn, flute) after a performance of Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4528.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_243.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung hugs Susan Ung, viola as Michael Lewanski, conductor and Ensemble Dal Niente (Mabel Kwan, piano, Tam Travers, violin, Chris Wild, violoncello, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Stephen Solook, percussion, and Emma Hospelhorn, flute) look on after a performance of Ung's Signing Inside Aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4529.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_244.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung acknowledges Susan Ung, viola as Michael Lewanski, conductor and Ensemble Dal Niente (Mabel Kwan, piano, Tam Travers, violin, Chris Wild, violoncello, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Stephen Solook, percussion, and Emma Hospelhorn, flute) look on after a performance of Ung's Signing Inside Aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4530.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_245.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung acknowledges Susan Ung, viola as Michael Lewanski, conductor and Ensemble Dal Niente (Mabel Kwan, piano, Tam Travers, violin, Chris Wild, violoncello, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Stephen Solook, percussion, and Emma Hospelhorn, flute) look on after a performance of Ung's Signing Inside Aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name ENSEMBLE DAL NIENTE with Chinary Ung Susan Ung.jpg Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_246.tif)
- Clarinetist Katie Schoepflin and pianist Mabel Kwan of Ensemble Dal Niente perform David Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4531.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_247.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski and Ensemble Dal Niente (Tam Travers, violin, Mabel Kwan, piano, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Magnus Andersson, guitar, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Chris Wild, violoncello, and Greg Beyer, percussion) perform Hans Abrahamsen's Winternacht at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4532.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_248.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski and Ensemble Dal Niente (Mabel Kwan, piano, Tam Travers, violin, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Magnus Andersson, guitar, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Chris Wild, violoncello, and Greg Beyer, percussion) acknowledge applause for a performance of Hans Abrahamsen's Winternacht at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4534.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_249.tif)
- Clarinetist Katie Schoepflin of Ensemble Dal Niente performs part of David Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4540.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_250.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski acknowledging applause with Ensemble Dal Niente (Chris Wild, violoncello, Greg Beyer, percussion, Stephen Solook, percussion, Mabel Kwan, piano, Tam Travers, violin, Susan Ung, viola, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, and Katie Schoepflin, clarinet) after a performance at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4541.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_251.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski acknowledging applause with Ensemble Dal Niente (Chris Wild, violoncello, Greg Beyer, percussion, Stephen Solook, percussion, Mabel Kwan, piano, Tam Travers, violin, Susan Ung, viola, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, and Katie Schoepflin, clarinet) after a performance at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name ENSEMBLE DAL NIENTE.jpg Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_252.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman leads Ensemble Signal (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Bill Solomon, percussion, Christa Robinson, oboe, Adrián Sandí, clarinet, Kelli Kathman, flute, and Ning Yu, piano) in a performance of Hans Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4542Ensemble SIGNAL.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_253.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman leads Ensemble Signal (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Bill Solomon, percussion, Christa Robinson, oboe, Adrián Sandí, clarinet, Kelli Kathman, flute, and Ning Yu, piano) in a performance of Hans Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4543Brad Lubman conductin Hans Ambrahamsen SCHNEE.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_254.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and Ensemble Signal (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, Lauren Radnofsky violoncello, Bill Solomon, percussion, Christa Robinson, oboe, Adrián Sandí, clarinet, and Kelli Kathman, flute) acknowledge composer Hans Abrahamsen after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4544.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_255.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and Ensemble Signal (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, Lauren Radnofsky violoncello, Bill Solomon, percussion, Christa Robinson, oboe, Adrián Sandí, clarinet, and Kelli Kathman, flute) acknowledge composer Hans Abrahamsen after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4545.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_256.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman hugs composer Hans Abrahamsen as Ensemble Signal (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, Lauren Radnofsky violoncello, Bill Solomon, percussion, Christa Robinson, oboe, Adrián Sandí, clarinet, and Kelli Kathman, flute) look on after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4546.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_257.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman hugs composer Hans Abrahamsen as Ensemble Signal (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, Lauren Radnofsky violoncello, Bill Solomon, percussion, Christa Robinson, oboe, Adrián Sandí, clarinet, and Kelli Kathman, flute) look on after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4547.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_258.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen hugs Courtney Orlando, violin as conductor Brad Lubman and other Ensemble Signal members (Isabel Hagen, viola and Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello) look on after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4548.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_259.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen acknowledges Ensemble Signal members (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, and Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello) as Brad Lubman looks on after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4549.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_260.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen acknowledges Ensemble Signal members (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, and Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello) as Brad Lubman looks on after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4552.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_261.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen acknowledges Ensemble Signal members (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, and Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello) as Brad Lubman looks on after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4553.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_262.tif)
- Ensemble Signal members (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, and Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello) and conductor Brad Lubman acknowledge composer Hans Abrahamsen after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4554.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_263.tif)
- Ensemble Signal members (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, and Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello) and conductor Brad Lubman acknowledge composer Hans Abrahamsen after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4556.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_264.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen acknowledges conductor Brad Lubman and Ensemble Signal (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Bill Solomon, percussion, Christa Robinson, oboe, Adrián Sandí, clarinet, and Kelli Kathman, flute) after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4559.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_265.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen and conductor Brad Lubman acknowledge Ensemble Signal (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Bill Solomon, percussion, Christa Robinson, oboe, Adrián Sandí, clarinet, Kelli Kathman. flute, and Ning Yu, piano) after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4560.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_266.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen and conductor Brad Lubman acknowledge Ensemble Signal (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Bill Solomon, percussion, Christa Robinson, oboe, Adrián Sandí, clarinet, Kelli Kathman. flute, and Ning Yu, piano) after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4561.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_267.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen, conductor Brad Lubman, and Ensemble Signal (Courtney Orlando, violin, Isabel Hagen, viola, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Bill Solomon, percussion, Christa Robinson, oboe, Adrián Sandí, clarinet, Kelli Kathman. flute, and Ning Yu, piano) acknowledge applause after a performance of Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4563.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_268.tif)
- Student composer Colin Tucker examines the score of his work, threshold at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name student composer Colin Tucker.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_269.tif)
- Väinö Jalkanen, piano and Malla Vivolin, flute of Ensemble Uusinta perform student composer Igor Coelho A.S. Marques' huithrothroy at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name huithrothroy (2016) student composer Igor Coelho A.S.Marques.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_270.tif)
- Maria Puusaari, violin, Max Savikangas, viola, and Pinja Laine, violoncello of Ensemble Uusinta perform student composer Colin Tucker's threshold at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name String Trio (2015) by student composer YoungWoo Yoo with Ensemble Uusinta.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_271.tif)
- Maria Puusaari, violin, Max Savikangas, viola, and Pinja Laine, violoncello of Ensemble Uusinta acknowledge applause after a performance of student composer Colin Tucker's threshold at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Ensemble Uusinta Maria Puusaari, violin-.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_272.tif)
- Student composer Colin Tucker acknowledges Maria Puusaari, violin, Max Savikangas, viola, and Pinja Laine, violoncello of Ensemble Uusinta after a performance of Tucker's threshold at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Ensemble Uusinta student composer Cilin Tucker.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_273.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars and Ensemble Uusinta (Malla Vivolin, flute, Marko Portin, clarinet, Maria Puusaari, violin, Max Savikangas, viola, and Pinja Laine, violoncello) perform student composer Ryan Suleiman's Up Close and from a distance at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Ensemble Uusinta Baird recital Hall Thursday 4pm.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_274.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars and Ensemble Uusinta (Malla Vivolin, flute, Marko Portin, clarinet, Maria Puusaari, violin, Max Savikangas, viola, and Pinja Laine, violoncello) acknowledge applause after a performance of student composer Ryan Suleiman's Up close and from a distance at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Ensemble Uusinta June in Buffalo 2016.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_275.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars and Ensemble Uusinta (Malla Vivolin, flute, Marko Portin, clarinet, Maria Puusaari, violin, Max Savikangas, viola, and Pinja Laine, violoncello) acknowledge student composer Ryan Suleiman after a performance of Suleiman's Up close and from a distance at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Ensemble Uusinta with student composer.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_276.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars and Ensemble Uusinta (Malla Vivolin, flute, Marko Portin, clarinet, Maria Puusaari, violin, Max Savikangas, viola, and Pinja Laine, violoncello) acknowledge applause after a performance of student composer Ryan Suleiman's Up close and from a distance at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Ensemble Uusinta student composer concert Thursday Baird Hall 4 pm.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_277.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars and Ensemble Uusinta (Väinö Jalkanen, piano, Malla Vivolin, flute, Max Savikangas, viola, and Pinja Laine, violoncello) perform student composer Peter Kramer's Waxen at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name JIB Ensemble Uusinta Baird Hall student composer concert.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_278.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars and Ensemble Uusinta (Väinö Jalkanen, piano, Malla Vivolin, flute, Max Savikangas, viola, and Pinja Laine, violoncello) acknowledge student composer Peter Kramer after a performance of Kramer's Waxen at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name student composer concert Baird Hall Thursday.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_279.tif)
- Student composers Igor Coelho A.S. Marques, Colin Tucker, Ryan Suleiman, Peter Kramer, and Young Woo Yoo acknowledge applause after a concert of their pieces at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name student composers Baird Hall Thursday.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_280.tif)
- Ensemble Uusinta (Jozsef Hars, conductor, Marko Portin, clarinet, Väinö Jalkanen, piano, Max Savikangas, viola, Pinja Laine, violoncello, Malla Vivolin, flute, and Maria Puusaari, violin) and student composers Igor Coelho A.S. Marques, Colin Tucker, Ryan Suleiman, Peter Kramer, and Young Woo Yoo acknowledge applause after a concert of student compositions at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name student composers Baird Hall JIB.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_281.tif)
- Ensemble Uusinta (Jozsef Hars, conductor, Marko Portin, clarinet, Väinö Jalkanen, piano, Max Savikangas, viola, Pinja Laine, violoncello, Malla Vivolin, flute, and Maria Puusaari, violin) and student composers Igor Coelho A.S. Marques, Colin Tucker, Ryan Suleiman, Peter Kramer, and Young Woo Yoo acknowledge applause after a concert of student compositions at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Ensemble Uusinta with student composers.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_282.tif)